

Personal

Name Ahmet Esat UGUR

Address Łukasiewicza 15/3, 50-369 Wrocław

Phone number +48 730023031

Email aeugur52@gmail.com

Date of birth **01-03-1995**

Place of birth Istanbul

Gender Male

Nationality **TURKISH**

Marital status SINGLE

Driving licence B

Profile

I am writing to apply for the position advertised in your organization. I enclose a completed job application, my certifications and resume.

The role is very appealing to me, and i believe that my strong technical experience, talent and education make me a highly competitive candidate for this position. My key strengths that would support my success in this position include:

- I have a corporate job experience.
- I strive continually for excellence.
- · I am very enthusiastic about moving as a team and developing skills.
- I provide exceptional contributions to customer service for all customers.

With Bachelor Degree study in Computer Science and Management, I have a comprehensive understanding of the full lifecycle for many projects. I also have an enthusiasm in learning and applying new techniques or technologies as appropriate. Please see my resume for additional information on my skills and experience.

I can be reached anytime via e-mail at aeugur52@gmail.com or by cell phone,+48 730-023-031.

Thank you for your time and consideration. I look forward to speak with you about this employment opportunity. Sincerely,

AHMET ESAT UGUR

Education and Qualifications

Sep 2013 - Jun 2015

Bachelor Degree

Turkish Air Force Academy, Istanbul

Oct 2019 - Present

Bachelor Degree

Politechnika Wrocławska, Wrocław

IT and Management

Work experience

Data Analyst

Dagize Law and Consultancy Ofiice, Istanbul

I was responsible for analyzing the files containing both personal and company information concerning the case of the advisors and taxpayers and submitting them to lawyers. I mostly used Ms Excel(VBA) while doing these tasks.

Jun 2018 - Aug 2018

Assistant Buyer

Decathlon Turkey, Istanbul

Jun 2013 - Aug 2013

Tourist Guide

The Istanbul Metropolitan Municipality, Istanbul

We were guiding tourists who asked for help on the streets in certain tourist attractions in Istanbul.

Interests

Chess, Scuba Diving, Pentathlon, Climbing, Foreign Languages, Basketball

Skills

AutoCad	• • • • •
Microsoft Excel	• • • • •
Python 3	• • • • •
Ms Office	• • • • •
Visual Basic	• • • • •
HTML & CSS	• • • • •
Team Work	• • • •
Mathematics	• • • • •
Communication	• • • • •
Problem Solving	• • • • •
Willingness to Learn	• • • • •

Languages

English					
Turkish	•	•	•	•	•
Polish	•	•			